My name is Michael Crowe
and I own Southwest Mushrooms.
Here we cultivate a wide variety
of gourmet and medicinal mushrooms.
I started when I was about fifteen,
I just got interested in mushrooms.
Most AI tools assume the user is in an office.
Growers, farmers, anyone running a real operation,
we don't get that. The connection is bad.
The data is private. The question has to be answered
in the next ten minutes, not after a sync.
Gemma 4 Mycelium is built on Google's Gemma 4.
It's the first open-source model in the Crowe Logic family.
The fine-tune comes from our commercial cultivation library:
Lion's Mane SOP, the Mushroom Grower volumes,
telemetry from our environmental engine.
Released under the Gemma Terms of Use.
Every operator I know has a question
they can't ask a chatbot a thousand miles away.
We started with mushrooms.
The next models in the Crowe Logic family
will start with whoever shows me their grow room next.
Built on Gemma. Made for the work.